<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<suppressions xmlns="https://jeremylong.github.io/DependencyCheck/dependency-suppression.1.3.xsd">
    <!-- Below are the supressions added fpr False Positive CVEs  -->
    <suppress  until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>CVE-2018-1258 we do not use Spring Method Security, so this does not affect us. see https://pivotal.io/security/cve-2018-1258.
            we are on latest Spring Framework version : 5.2.2.RELEASE : https://github.com/spring-projects/spring-framework/wiki/Spring-Framework-Versions
            This is confirmed as false positive and hence it is suppressed (https://github.com/jeremylong/DependencyCheck/issues/2952)
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2018-1258</cve>
    </suppress>

    <!-- Below are the supressions that are made for the CVEs which occur in the latest version -->
    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>
            <![CDATA[This CVE appears in the latest version of wiremock, WireMock 2.27.2 JRE 8 embeds jquery-3.4.1.min.js. see(https://github.com/tomakehurst/wiremock/issues/1417)]]></notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-11022</cve>
        <cve>CVE-2020-11023</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>
            In logback version 1.2.7 and prior versions, an attacker with the required privileges to edit configurations
            files could craft a malicious configuration allowing to execute arbitrary code loaded from LDAP servers.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2021-42550</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>
            Improper Restriction of XML External Entity Reference in GitHub repository liquibase/liquibase prior to 4.8.0.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-0839</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>
            jackson-databind before 2.13.0 allows a Java StackOverflow exception and denial of service via a large depth
            of nested objects.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2020-36518</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>spring boot issue, upgrading to new version broke functional tests.</notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22965</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>Spring Framework older unsupported versions, it is possible for a user to provide a specially
            crafted SpEL expression that may cause a denial of service condition</notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22950</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>In Spring Framework versions 5.3.0 - 5.3.16 and older unsupported versions, it is possible for a user to
            provide a specially crafted SpEL expression that may cause a denial of service condition.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2016-1000027</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>In Spring Framework versions 5.3.0 - 5.3.18, 5.2.0 - 5.2.20, and older unsupported versions, the patterns for
            disallowedFields on a DataBinder are case sensitive which means a field is not effectively protected unless it is
            listed with both upper and lower case for the first character of the field, including upper and lower case for the
            first character of all nested fields within the property path.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-22968</cve>
    </suppress>
    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>
            In Apache Tomcat 10.1.0-M1 to 10.1.0-M16, 10.0.0-M1 to 10.0.22, 9.0.30 to 9.0.64 and 8.5.50 to 8.5.81 the
            Form authentication example in the examples web application displayed user provided data without filtering,
            exposing a XSS vulnerability. It can looked into in the next major releases, if any latest versions released.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-34305</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
        <notes>
            Versions of the Amazon AWS Apache Log4j hotpatch package before log4j-cve-2021-44228-hotpatch-1.3.5 are
            affected by a race condition that could lead to a local privilege escalation. CVE-2022-33915 occured,
            despite latest versions used.
        </notes>
        <cve>CVE-2022-33915</cve>
    </suppress>
    
    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
      <notes>
        The RipudamanKaushikDal/projects repository through 2022-04-03 on GitHub allows absolute path traversal
        because the Flask send_file function is used unsafely.
      </notes>
      <cve>CVE-2022-31569</cve>
    </suppress>

    <suppress until="2022-09-30">
      <notes>
        The nrlakin/homepage repository through 2017-03-06 on GitHub allows absolute path traversal because the
        Flask send_file function is used unsafely.
      </notes>
      <cve>CVE-2022-31548</cve>
    </suppress>
    <!-- Supression group ends here  -->
</suppressions>
